2013年春天
In the spring of 2013,
巴尼和罗宾距喜结连理只有几周之遥了
Barney and Robin were just weeks away from tying the knot.
可在某些大事上 他们还未做决定
But there were still some pretty big issues they hadn't agreed on.
领养
Adoption.
我不知道啊
I don't know.
只有领养才说得通
It's the only thing that makes sense.
我真的不敢相信你会不接受
I can't... I can't believe you're not open to it.
好吧 那就试试吧
Okay. Let's try it.
不行 竖着的第27个词就不合适了
Nope, it doesn't work with 27 down.
嘿 考虑到咱婚礼快到了
Hey, with the wedding so close,
也许我们该讨论下
maybe we should talk about
结婚后住在哪儿吧
where we're going to live.
好吧 够了
Fine, enough.
不用求我了
Stop begging.
我们就住这儿
We'll live here.
但这算你欠我的
But you owe me.
是啊 我说不清
Yeah, I don't know...
就是我不是完全喜欢
there's just a lot of things
你公寓里的一些东西
I don't totally love about your apartment.
比如什么
Like what?
好吧 举个例子
Well, for example, why is
为什么你的床好像放在类似铁轨的东西上
your bed on what look like train tracks?
你太厉害了
You were wonderful.
要是连如何取悦女人都不知道
Well, you don't get to be a state-certified orgasmologist
怎么能成为获得国家认可的高潮大师呢
without learning how to please a woman.
你不介意我留下来过夜吧
You don't mind if I spend the night, do you?
呃 不这样的话
Um, how else are we gonna
我们怎么能更深一步地了解对方呢
get to know each other on a deeper level?
不好意思
Excuse me,
我得把今晚的高潮报告上交给董事会
I just have to log tonight's orgasms with the licensing board.
妞-走-人 睡眠系统
The Ho-be-gone Sleep System
斯丁森出品 专利申请中
by Stinson, patent pending.
墙的另外一面究竟是什么
What-what is on the other side of the wall?
那些小妞们都去哪了
Where do the hos go?
我哪知道 你以为我是装修公司啊
What am I, a contractor?
我们的婚姻要有个崭新的开端
We-we need to go into this marriage with a fresh start.
你说咱俩一起找个新房子住如何
What do you say we find a new place together?
我爱你
I love you.
如果那能让你高兴的话
And if that will make you happy,
咱就找吧
then let's do it.
喔 那我得在一个我没睡过妞的地方找个公寓
Wow, so we need to find an apartment where I haven't banged someone?
你觉得克利夫兰怎么样
How do you feel about Cleveland?
哈 哈
Ha, ha.
不行 那有泰德妈妈
Nope. Ted's mom.
老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N　　  　　　　第八季  第十九集\N
S08E19 The Fortress
翻译: @Big-Fudge @阿狸小H @麟礡\N@纷扬jas-mine @卟哒哒伽马 @苏赛晒小花\N校对: @苏赛晒小花 @阿狸小H
压制: @Big-Fudge\N统筹+后期: @神RoyShiCheng @苏赛晒小花
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献
嘘
Shh...
你替莉莉给马文唱催眠曲 唱得不错啊
Nice job filling in for Lily on Marvin's lullaby.
谢谢 就是唱小马那段时我好像快了点
Thanks, but I came in early on the horsie.
笨死了
Stupid!
不 你真的把莉莉的部分唱的很好了
No, you really nailed all of Lily's parts.
我三个星期前才练好
It's been three weeks since I have.
因为莉莉工作的事 我都没怎么见她
I barely see her anymore 'cause of this new job.
知道什么能让你开心起来吗
Well, you know what might cheer you up?
今晚有伍德沃斯庄园的新剧集哦
There's a new Woodworthy Manor on tonight.
伍德沃斯庄园是一部
Woodworthy Manor
讲述20世纪初英国上层阶级故事的电视剧
was a show about an upper class English estate at the beginning of the 20th century.
我的天 你不可能说的是...
My word! You can't possibly mean...
可我是这样想的
But I do!
自从伊斯特布鲁克太太继承给了玛丽米德子爵夫人
With the succession of Lady Eastbrooke to Viscountess of Marlyemead,
我们的侄子博德里克就成了维泽施德伯爵
our cousin Baldrick becomes the Earl of Witherstead.
维泽施德伯爵啊
The Earl of Witherstead!
我都在论坛上预测过15遍了
I only posted that prediction 15 times on the forums!
不行 我不能
No, I can't.
我答应莉莉了 要等她一起看
I promised Lily that I would wait and watch it with her.
问题在于 船长大人
Problem is, the Captain.
莉莉刚开始为一位有怪癖的
Lily had just started a job
亿万富翁 船长大人 做艺术顾问
as the art consultant for an eccentric billionaire, the Captain.
啊嗬
Ahoy.
瑞德虎克有个炙手可热的新艺术家
There's a hot new artist in Red Hook.
瑞德虎克位于布鲁克林
他熔了世界各国的货币铸成一座雕像
He's molded world currency into a sculpture
雕像是一位无情的大富豪在穷人身上拉翔
of a soulless plutocrat defecating on the poor.
这是对资本主义的无情控诉
A scathing indictment of capitalism.
我最高愿意出20万美元
I'll go as high as $200K
如果六个月后我转手 价钱能翻倍的话
as long as you think I can flip it for double in six months.
遵命 船长大人
Aye, aye, Cap'n.
不好意思
Sorry.
啊嗬
Ahoy.
这儿有一幅画工超赞的印象主义静物画
here's this gorgeously delicate impressionist still life,
让我想起莫奈画的池中睡莲
reminiscent of Monet's water lilies.
在哪儿呢
Where is it?
里克斯岛上
Rikers Island.
纽约著名监狱
这位艺术家正因为恶性谋杀
The artist is serving two consecutive life sentences
被判处两项终身监禁
for aggravated homicide.
我最高愿意为这幅画
I'm willing to go as high as
出六条烟和一坛子茅房酒
six cartons of cigarettes and a jug of toilet wine.
茅房酒指监狱犯人自酿的酒 通常藏在马桶的水箱里
我负担太大了
Is it a strain,
时不时感觉自己就像一个单亲爸爸
feeling like a single dad at times?
的确 但是莉莉正努力在新工作领域站稳脚跟
Sure, but Lily's been busting her butt at this new job.
她又不是在外面吃喝玩乐
It's not like she's been out there partying.
天 我有点醉了
Man, I'm 'faced.
我吃了一大堆鱼子酱
I ate a ton of caviar,
还是没能把我的香槟都炸出来
but it soaked up none of the champagne.
鱼子酱配香槟会有口中噼噼啪啪的响个不停的美妙感
-这就是周一啊  -是啊
-Mondays, right? -Yeah.
你什么时候开始戴眼镜了
When did you get glasses?
噢
Oh...
你是说我的无敌防眩光眼镜
you mean my glare reduction lunettes.
它能帮我从自命不凡的烂货中挑出真正的天才
Yeah. They help me discern genius from pretentious crap.
你在买这副眼镜的时候
Too bad you weren't wearing those glasses
没有戴上这副识别眼镜 真是太可惜了
when you bought those glasses.
好了 听着 宝贝
Well, listen, baby, I-I'm just
我很高兴见到你
happy to see you.
如果你不是太累的话
And if you're not too tired,
我们今晚可以一起看伍德沃斯庄园
maybe we could watch Woodworthy Manor tonight.
可以呀
I'd love to.
太好了 因为我想到了一个
Great! Because I've come up
特别好玩的小游戏
with a fun little game.
我做了一些无花果布丁
I made figgy pudding
放在小酒杯里
and I put it in shot glasses.
每次剧中说到
And every time they say,
"夫人会不高兴的"
"The dowager will be less than pleased,"
你就得
you have to...
哦
Oh.
呃
Ugh...
啊嗬
Ahoy.
一个两米多高穿异性服装的柬埔寨人
A seven-foot-tall cross-dressing Cambodian
在往BQE的一个公告牌上
is throwing glitter and fish guts
扔亮粉和鱼内脏
at a billboard on the B.Q.E.
B.Q.E. 连接纽约布鲁克林区和皇后区的高速公路
那他是某个概念艺术画家吗
So he's some sort of conceptual painter?
不是 只是一个上了地方新闻的疯子
No, no, just a crazy person on the local news.
我以为你听了会笑呢
I thought you might have a laugh.
你已经下班了 别紧张
You're off the clock, relax.
我要把这个买下来
I must own it.
遵命 船长大人
Aye, aye, Cap'n.
嘿 你找到卖房子的经纪人了吗
Hey, did you find a Realtor to sell this place yet?
罗宾 经纪人只会把这间公寓
Robin, a Realtor's just gonna
卖给出价最高的人
give it to the highest bidder.
我想卖给值得拥有的人
I need this place to go to someone worthy.
我已经做了一些调查
And I've made some inquiries.
巴尼
Barney?
吾儿
My son.
巴尼 别玩漂浮的乔•艾尔头了
Barney, enough with the floating Jor-El head
这是超人的孤独堡垒里的
from the Fortress of Solitude in Superman, okay?
这太老套了
It's getting old.
我只用这个来说非常重要的事情
I only use it to say really important stuff.
上次你用这个是告诉我
Last time you used it to tell me
云狄斯新出了辣味版的培根汉堡
Wendy's had introduced a spicy version of "The Baconator."
Wendy's 云狄斯 美国第二大汉堡包快餐连锁店
就是这个意思
Exactly.
好了 吾儿
And now, my son...
时辰已至 吾将赠与你
it is time for me to bestow on you...
我们就不能像正常人那样面对面交流吗
Can we just talk face-to-face like normal people?
泰德 你就
Ted, just...
配合一下
just...
好吗
okay?
吾儿
My son,
时辰已至 吾将赠与你
it is time for me to bestow on you...
把门关上
Close the door.
不 这也
No. This is...
我的天啊 你就不能好好的
Oh, my God, can you just be cool?
哪怕一次 求你了
Once? Please?
就这一次
Just once?
配合一下会死吗
Can you just once be cool?
就一次
Once?
求你了
Please?
吾儿
My son...
许多年来
for many years
这套公寓都是我巴尼超人的孤独堡垒
this apartment has been my Fortress of Barnitude.
但现在是时候让我
But now the time has come
把它传下去了
for me to pass it on.
不久 这个地方就会变成
Soon, this place will become
你的"泰德超人的孤独堡垒"
your "Fortress of Soli-Ted."
巴尼 哪怕你用
Barney, I wouldn't
普瑞来 阿莫西林和圣水刷洗这里的每一个角落
live here even if you scrubbed every inch of this place
我也不会住进来
with Purell, amoxicillin and holy water.
Purell 普瑞来 美国洗手液品牌
好吧
Fine.
但我觉得我们都同意
But I think we can both agree,
如果能用乔•艾尔摄像机能让我的
it would be totally awesome to see
那玩意儿漂浮在空中绝对是好棒的
my deal floating around all huge-like on the big Jor-El cam.
等一下
Hold on.
现在堡垒里有点冷
Now, it's a little cold here in the Fortress,
所以别因为这个
so don't judge...
泰德 等等
Ted, wait.
你做了什么
What did you...
你把... 好了 这样不好玩
That's... okay, that's not funny.
泰德 开门
Ted, open the...
呃 墙壁在向我逼近
Uh... walls closing in.
我没法呼吸了
I can't... can't breathe.
必须
Must...
展示那玩意
show deal...
用乔•艾尔摄像机
on Jor-El cam...
我...
I...
这样看来我只好永远保留这套公寓了 晚安
Oh, well, guess I'm keeping this place forever, good night.
等等 给我等一下 这样就完了
Wait a... wait a minute, that's it?
泰德没兴趣买你的公寓
Ted wasn't interested in buying your apartment,
你就放弃了吗
so you just gave up?
巴尼 我抛弃了自己
Barney, I gave up my
位于曼哈顿上西区的
beautiful two-bedroom apartment
不用交房租的两室公寓
on the Upper West Side that was rent-free
房东还亲自手洗我的高档衣服
and the landlord hand-washed all my delicates.
这可能是我不用交房租的原因
Which is probably why it was rent-free.
重点是
The point is,
我所有内衣都要重新买
I need to buy all new underwear,
你也答应我们一起换个新地方住
and you agreed that we would find a new place together.
天啊 巴尼
Oh, God, Barney,
恋爱是需要互相信任和妥协的
relationships are about trust and compromise.
你不能只是
You can't just...
啊 你死定了
Oh, you are so dead.
别让我找到方法出来
If I ever figure a way out of here,
我会让你生不如死的
I will make your life a living...
我和莉莉真的很需要出去约个会
Lily and I really need this night out.
丰盛精致的晚餐和芭蕾表演
A big fancy dinner and the ballet.
谢谢你能帮忙照顾孩子
Thank you so much for babysitting.
嘿 一小时三刀呢 谢谢你才对
Hey, three bucks an hour, thank you.
喂 宝贝
Oh, hey, baby.
我正要出门
Yeah, I'm just on my way out.
如果你早到了
If you get there before...
别这样 不是吧
Come on, really?
之后见
I'll see you later.
船长吗
Captain?
真遗憾 兄弟 不过
I'm sorry, dude. But, hey,
你可以这样想
look at it this way:
至少你不用去看芭蕾表演了啊
now you don't have to go to the ballet.
把你脑袋从菊花里拔出来使一下好吗 泰德
Get your head out of your ass, Ted.
根本就没有什么芭蕾表演
There was no ballet.
我们就打算溜进你公寓来一炮
We were gonna sneak into your apartment and bang.
好吧 知道有什么可以
Well, you know what might
让我们忘掉这些烦心事吗
take both our minds off that?
稍稍看一集
A little, uh...
伍德沃斯庄园
Woodworthy Manor.
不 这不行
No, I-I-I can't.
我答应过莉莉
I-I promised Lily
要等着她一起看的
that I would wait and watch it with her.
要是我先看了 就好像背叛了她一样
And I feel like I'd be cheating on her.
好吧好吧 我懂的
Sure, sure, sure, sure, I get all that.
只不过
It's just, um...
你要知道 今晚他们终于要找出那个
You know, tonight they're gonna finally reveal
而陷害扫烟囱工说他偷了庄园主人
who framed the chimney sweep
斯塔德夏尔的鹅莓的凶手了
for stealing Lord Stoutshire's gooseberries.
还要角逐出
And reveal the winner of
当地园艺大赛的冠军
the local gardening competition.
我完全猜不透他们怎样才能
I don't know how they're going to pack
把这么多剧情集中到一集里面
all that action into one episode.
啊哦
Oops.
不行啊 泰德
No, Ted, you know
-我答应了莉莉  -嘘 别说话
-I promised Lily, I... -Shh, shh, shh.
顺其自然吧
Just let it happen.
这周晚些时候 巴尼回家时发现
Later that week, Barney came home to discover
罗宾给他准备了一个小惊喜
that Robin had a little surprise waiting for him.
-含羞草吗  -是啊
-Mimosas? -Mm-hmm.
Mimosas 因为颜色像含羞草而命名的鸡尾酒
刚烤的饼干的香味
Freshly-baked cookie smell?
还有穿红色运动衣的中年妇女
A middle-aged woman in a red blazer?
我明白了
I see what this is.
你总算同意我纵酒狂欢啦
You finally green-lit my orgy idea!
真好
Okay.
这是场家庭招待会 巴尼
It's an open house, Barney.
跟你的堡垒说再见吧
Say good-bye to your fortress.
要不是因为我们要狂欢
If we weren't about to have an orgy,
我肯定会对你发火的
I'd be so mad at you right now.
如果你们跟随我到卧室
If you'll follow me into the bedroom,
会看到很棒的实木家具哦
I'll show you some beautiful woodwork.
我现在太生气 都懒得吐槽 曾有多少无知少女
I am way too upset right now to point out how many women
在卧室里见过很棒的"实木家具"
have seen some beautiful woodwork in there.
也指小鸡鸡
愤怒自我击掌
Angry self five!
啊
Rah!
罗宾
Robin,
我不允许你卖掉公寓
I did not agree to this.
你必须允许
Yes, you did.
我搬出我的公寓
That is why I gave up my apartment.
不是为了住进一个病菌滋生
Not so I could live in a disease-riddled bang pad
上门荡妇阴魂不散的淫窝
haunted by the ghosts of your ex-skanks.
浴室是意大利大理石的哟
The bathrooms are Italian marble.
你好啊 老兄
Hello, old bean.
今晚棒极了 对吧
Jolly good evening, isn't it?
你们在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
而且你说话怎么跟麦当娜似的
And why do you sound like Madonna?
罗宾让我们都来转转
Uh, Robin asked us all to come here
假装我们是很喜欢这公寓的潜在买主
and pretend that we are prospective buyers who love this apartment.
我受到伍德沃斯庄园中
And inspired by a character
一个角色的启发 决定扮演
on Woodworthy Manor, I've decided to play
埃姆斯布瑞•波斯尔思韦特
Emsbry Postlethwaite,
一位帅气迷人内心却厌恶自己生活的板球运动员
a handsome cricket player who secretly hates his life.
你没必要当什么板球运动员
You don't have to be a cricket player.
跟埃姆斯布瑞的爸爸说去吧
Tell that to Emsbry's father.
抱歉
Sorry!
我来了
Oh...
我去看了些地铁流浪汉的涂鸦作品
I was checking out some mole people's graffiti art
我的披肩还被地铁勾住了
and my cape got caught on the F train.
来
Oh.
亲亲
Bisou bisou.
哇 好可爱的宝宝
Oh, what a cute baby.
他叫什么名字啊
What's his name?
马尔文
Marvin.
为了纪念我父亲
For my father.
噢 这好贴心啊
Oh, that's so sweet.
你们俩已经在这一带看很多公寓了吗
Have you two been looking at a lot of places in this neighborhood?
噢 事实上他们不是...
Oh, actually they're not...
是 我们看过了
Yes, we have.
什么
What?
我跟我丈夫埃姆斯布瑞爱死这一片地区了
My husband Emsbry and I just love this area.
我是一位帅气迷人内心却厌恶自己生活的板球运动员
I'm a cricket player who secretly hates his life.
你在干什么啊
What are you doing?
鉴于你再一次迟到了
Well, you were late yet again,
我决定和泰德做一次角色扮演
and so I'm gonna do this little scene study with Ted.
你问为什么 因为他随时在我身边
Why? Because he's there for me.
假装你结婚了
Pretending you're married?
这离你要证明的观点也太远了吧
That's going a little far to prove your point, isn't it?
打扰一下 但是你说同性恋情侣们结婚
Excuse me, but I think it's offensive to suggest
只是为了证明某种观点也太无礼了吧
the only reason gay people get married is to prove a point.
不×5
No, no, no, no, no.
我不是那个意思
I didn't... that's not what I...
谢谢你 姐们 看来需要找人来给
Thank you, sister-- somebody needs
这位女士的思想安一块倒车镜
to get this lady's mind a rearview mirror
因为她的思维在倒退
because she is thinking in reverse. Mm-hmm.
恨就一个字 我只说一次
Hate is a four-letter word.
我没有 我投票给了...
I didn't... I voted for...
噢 这是安全系统的一部分吗
Oh, is this part of a security system?
算是吧
Sort of.
它和门口的擦鞋垫是连起来的 你看
It's connected to the welcome mat. You see...
假设你带回家的小妞
Let's say the young lady you're bringing home
穿的冬装
is dressed for winter.
在这个面板里面
Under those layers,
可能有个不幸的消息等着你
an unwelcome surprise could await you.
在擦鞋垫下面我藏了一个
The scale with body fat calculator
人体脂肪测量秤
I've hidden under the welcome mat
可以确保我不会睡让我后悔的妞
makes sure you never have banger's remorse.
肥妞快走
The Heavy Set Go
斯丁森出品 专利申请中
by Stinson, patent pending.
因为卧室里只有一种丰满的东西是你想要的
'Cause there's only one kind of chubby you want in the bedroom.
我说的对吧 大家
Am I right, people?
这家伙知道我在说什么
This guy knows what I'm talking about.
不是我想教你和埃姆斯布瑞怎么养"你们的"孩子
I don't want to tell you and Emsbry how to raise your child,
但如果你一直让他打盹的话
but I think if you keep letting him nap,
他会整夜睡不着的
he's gonna be up all night.
真是搞笑 听起来好像你最近有
Funny, you sound like someone who's been
陪着他入睡一样
around for his bedtime lately.
嗯 有人能给这位女士一家店面
Uh, can somebody get this lady a storefront
好让她专注于自己的事情吗
'cause she needs to mind her own business, mm-kay?
你能歇会儿吗
Would you stop it?
噢 对 对 因为这是你的抉择
Oh, right, right, because it's a choice.
你们知道什么不用抉择吗
You know what's not a choice?
充满基情地享用这个厨房
Being gay for this kitchen.
打开方式有点不太对 重点是
That came out wrong-- the point is,
看看这个超赞的公寓吧
let's focus on this awesome apartment.
你说得对
You're right.
看看这个传说中的等离子电视吧
Look at that fabulous plasma television.
我的前夫 那个从不支持我事业的家伙
My ex-husband, who never supported my career,
会爱死用这个来看维京人
would love to watch the Vikings never win a Super Bowl
在历史上从来没赢过的超级碗比赛
in franchise history on that thing.
-岂有此理  -别让她戳中了你的怒点
-How dare you. -Don't let her push your buttons.
对
Right.
我才不在意什么橄榄球赛呢
I don't care about football.
我更算得上是个
I'm more of a...
伍德沃斯庄园剧迷
Woodworthy Manor fan.
我非常享受那一夜看剧的美好时光
I very much enjoyed watching it the other night.
和埃姆斯布瑞一起
With Emsbry.
你不会吧
Oh, you didn't.
是 我们看了
Yeah, oh, yeah.
我知道是谁故意水淹了
I know who deliberately overwatered
琪尔斯布瑞夫人那获过奖的玫瑰
Lady Chillsbury's prize-winning roses.
他们一整季都在为那个真相做铺垫
They have been building to that reveal all season,
马修 你敢再往下说
Marshall, don't you tell me...
是帕尔森•斯莫尔斯比
It was Parson Smallsby.
哇 风景不错
Wow, great view.
而且是可定制的哟
And customizable.
假设你承诺给一个女孩
Let's say you promised a girl
一场惊喜旅行
a surprise trip
到地球上最浪漫的地方
to the most romantic place on Earth.
不准偷看哦
No peeking.
哇 我们一定到了很远的地方
Wow, we must've gone far.
在你的私人飞机上待了快有六个小时了
We were on your private jet for, like, six hours.
是啊
Well,
你一定不是戴着耳塞乘着公交
You definitely weren't on a bus to Delaware
来回了一趟特拉华州 我只能告诉你这么多
and back wearing earplugs, I'll tell you that much.
看到眼前的美景时你一定会觉得
And I think you'll agree it was worth the wait
一切等待都是值得的
once you see the view.
亲爱的 我们到啦
Et voila ma cherie.
噢 我的天哪
Oh, my God.
你带我飞到了维加斯
You flew me to Vegas?
这是 这是巴黎
It's, um... it's Par...
算了 管用就行 无所谓啦
Well, hey, whatever works, whatever...
风景之屋
The Room With a Screw
斯丁森出品 专利申请中
by Stinson, patent pending.
我看懂你的这些把戏了
I know what you're trying to do.
你就是想把这些人都吓跑
You're trying to drive people away.
不 我才没有呢 我只是
No, I'm not-- I'm just trying
卖弄下这套公寓独一无二的特征
to show off all of its one-of-a-kind features.
看 看 我这儿还有 威尼斯
See, see, there's also, uh, Venice.
尼亚加拉大瀑布
Niagara Falls,
非洲之旅
African safari.
哦
Oh...
还有我的最爱
and my favorite...
怎么样
Huh?
让女孩以为自己在乎的人都已化为灰烬
Nothing gets a girl to go from "On the fence"
没有什么比这更快的方法
to "On all fours" Faster than thinking
让她从"犹豫不决"转变到"坚定不移"了
everyone she's ever held dear is a glowing pile of ash.
蘑菇云击掌
Mushroom cloud five.
我喜欢你的口音
I love you accent.
谢谢
Thank you.
我练了整整一早上了
I practiced it all morning.
你真可爱
You are adorable.
那个马修真是个幸运的男人
That Marshall's a lucky man.
哦 你真是招人喜欢
Well, aren't you ducky?
说真的 如果你是直男
Seriously if you were straight,
我一定为你倾倒
I'd be all over you.
哼
Huh.
这是什么
What's this?
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
史上最好的东西
Only the best thing ever.
假设你和一个女生过了愉快的一夜
Let's say you had a wonderful night with a girl, but now
她有点像吃完避孕药一样 磨叽着不走
she's turning into a bit of a morning-after pill.
看到了吧 我们要延长坡道
See? We need to extend the chute
再加一个着陆点
and add a landing spot.
你还说用假人测试是浪费时间
And you said testing it with a dummy was a waste of time.
不 我说的是"打扮这假人"是浪费时间
No, I said "Dressing the dummy" Was a waste of time.
贱人山的求生通道
The Escape From Bitch Mountain
斯丁森出品 专利申请中
by Stinson, patent pending.
他开玩笑呢 这只是 你知道
He's kidding, it's just, you know,
以防失火
in case of fire.
不是的 但是很高兴你正好提到了火
No, but I'm glad you mentioned fire.
看到那些烟雾探测器了吗
See those smoke detectors?
念出这些话
Say these words.
"我想要更进一步的承诺"
"I'm looking for a deeper commitment."
"我太累了""我们来抱抱吧"也会激活它
It's also triggered by "I'm too tired," "Let's snuggle,"
还有"我月经晚了一周"
and "I'm a week late."
巴尼 我身上都湿了
Barney, I'm getting wet.
说这句就能把它关掉
And that turns it off.
好吧 别说了
Look, just stop talking.
我们已经做好决定了
We've made up our minds.
哦 好吧 谢谢你们来参观
Oh, well, thanks for taking a look.
我来送你们出去
I'll walk you out.
我们买了
We'll take it.
只要你们不用紫外光灯 住在这里一定会超幸福的
If you never get a black light, you'll be so happy here.
紫外光灯会照出残留"小蝌蚪"的痕迹
太好了 太好了
Yes, yes!
天堂里的烦恼吗
Trouble in paradise?
《天堂里的烦恼》婚外恋电影
我们有个孩子
We have a child together.
真不敢相信你居然没等我一起看伍德沃斯庄园
I can't believe you watched Woodworthy Manor without me.
真不敢相信你居然生我的气
I can't believe that you're mad at me.
我老婆和基友都把我抛弃了
I've been abandoned by my wife and my gay companion.
如果我打羽毛球时候把一只眼睛弄瞎了
If I get blinded in one eye by a badminton shuttlecock,
那我就也成了艾斯特布鲁克庄主了
you might as well call me Lord Esterbrooke.
你背着我看了最新一集吗
You watched the new one without me?
被人背叛很不爽吧 埃姆斯布瑞
Betrayal stings, doesn't it, Emsbry?
嘿
Hey.
嘿 听着
Hey. Listen.
不 我先说
No, me first.
我考虑了一下
I've been thinking
想明白了一些事
and I realized something.
孤独堡垒是超人独处的地方
The Fortress of Solitude is where Superman went to be alone.
我永远都不想再一个人了
And I never want to be alone again.
谢谢 巴尼 那真是
Thank you, Barney, that really...
然后我想起了超人第二部
But then I remembered in Superman II,
超人为了露易丝•莱恩放弃了他的所有能力
Superman gave up all his powers to be with Lois Lane,
在那之后 老实说他就是个废人
and he was honestly kind of a vag after that.
哥们 能不能停一下
Oh, buddy, just quit while...
然后 超人第三部
Now, Superman III was
简直就是一部灾难
a complete train wreck totally.
你想说什么
What's your point?
想说 我爱你
that I love you.
还有
And...
我要为你放弃我的公寓
I'm giving up my apartment for you.
还有超人系列电影的水平参差不齐
And that the Superman films are uneven.
我真的很感动 巴尼 但是
I really appreciate that, Barney, but...
恭喜啊 你们入手了这间超赞的公寓
Congrats. You guys are getting a fantastic apartment.
我知道这里的一些地方有一点点奇怪
I mean, I know some of the features are a little weird.
一点点吗
A little?
我们会把这里都扒光
We're gonna rip this thing
拆成毛坯房
down to the studs.
我明白
I get it.
但是 我是说 还是有些值得保留的地方
But, I mean, some things might be worth saving.
我可没看出来 没有
I don't see any. No.
你没看出来
You don't see any?
当然这里的一些东西是有些吓人
Sure some of the stuff in here is creepy,
但也非常有才啊
but it's also brilliant.
我是说 很多天才都有些古怪
I mean, a lot of geniuses were kind of pervy.
看看托马斯•爱迪生
Look at Thomas Edison
不然你以为灯泡怎么会是胸部的形状呢
why do you think that lightbulbs are boob-shaped?
好吧 我们要把这个地方彻底拆掉
Yeah, we're taking a wrecking ball to this place
建成个真正适合人类的地方
and turning it into something actually fit for humans.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
出去
Get out!
巴尼超人的孤独堡垒不卖了
The Fortress of Barnitude is no longer for sale.
还有你的老公一下午一直盯着我的屁股看
Also your husband has been staring at my ass
所以别装高风亮节了
all afternoon so don't act all high-and-mighty.
你拒绝了他们
You turned them down?
是啊 如果我要求你改变太多
Yeah. If I ask you to change too many things about yourself,
你就不是我爱上的那个人了
you're not gonna be the man I fell in love with.
所以 我接受并欣赏你
Turns out, I accept and appreciate
包括你最猥琐 最可怕 最反社会的阴暗面
even the grossest, creepiest, most sociopathic parts of you.
某人刚才好像已经把结婚誓言写好了哦
Sounds like somebody just wrote her vows.
是船长
It's the Captain.
啊嗬
Ahoy.
中央公园的动物园里有一匹斑马
There's a zebra at the Central Park Zoo
有着对摄影非常敏锐的蹄子
who's got quite a keen hoof at photography.
说来好笑 他竟然对颜色很在行 现在
Ironically, he's great with color. Now...
船长 我会去看看的 但不是今晚
Captain, I'll check it out, just not tonight.
我需要些时间陪陪我的丈夫
I need to spend some time with my husband.
你确定吗
You sure?
我知道 我这样忙于工作 你挺不容易的
I know it's been tough, me working this much,
我估计自己对艺术家气派的追求也有点过火了
and I guess I went a little overboard with the whole artsy thing.
我知道
I know.
你那披肩
The cape.
我的披肩怎么了
What about my cape?
我很喜欢
I love it.
而且我知道 你热爱这份工作
And I... I know that you love this job.
我应该更支持你的 我只是想你了
I should be more supportive-- I just miss you.
我也想你
I miss you, too.
嗨 伙计们
Hey, guys.
-嗨  -嗨
-Hey. -Hey.
你们都好幸运
You guys are all so lucky.
我什么时候才能找到真爱呢
When am I gonna find something real?
埃姆斯布瑞 想不想试试和女人在一起是什么感觉
Well, Emsbry, ready to see what it's like to be with a woman?
万事总有第一次嘛
I suppose there's a first time for everything.
-去吧  -吾儿
-Go ahead. -My son.
你们确定我俩会喜欢伍德沃斯庄园吗
Are you guys sure we're gonna like this Woodworthy Manor show?
是啊 听起来有点无聊
Yeah, it sounds kind of boring.
有点无聊
Kind of boring?
快点坐下吧 但相信我吧 绝对精彩得让你坐不住
Grab a seat guys, but trust me, you're only gonna need the edge.
好了 先讲一段背景故事
Ah-ha, all right, now, a little backstory.
斯塔德夏尔小姐的槌球及踝靴事业已经发展壮大了
Lady Stoutshire has developed a serious case of croquet ankle
厨子布特布拉什夫人找不到足够的栗子
and the cook Mrs. Bootbrush can't find enough chestnuts
来喂圣克里斯宾节的鹅
for a proper St. Crispin's Day goose.
一起看吧
Let's watch.
我爱你
I love you.
我手腕摔坏了
My wrist is broken.
-那也值了  -嗷
-Worth it. -Ow.
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看